(Howard:)I believe it's time for me
to turn my head and cough.
- What is your move?
- I'm going to use the mirror technique.
She brushes her hair back, I brush mine.
She shrugs, I shrug.
(Howard:)Subconsciously, she's thinking,
"We're in sync. We belong together."
(Leonard:)Where do you get this stuff?
(Howard:)You know, psychology journals,
Internet research.
(Howard:)And there's this great show on VH1
about how to pick up girls.
(Raj:)Oh, if only I had his confidence.
(Raj:)I have such difficulty
speaking to women...
(Raj:)...or around women,
or at times even effeminate men.
(Howard:)If that's a working stethoscope...
(Howard:)...maybe you'd like to hear
my heart skip a beat.
(Howard:)No, thanks.
(Howard:)No, seriously, you can.
I have transient idiopathic arrhythmia.
[UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF GIANTS'
"GOT NOTHING" PLAYS ON STEREO]
So take my money
Take my money
I wanna get to know Penny's friends.
I just...
(Leonard:)I don't know
how to talk to these people.